Come with me.
Er Ni offered to help.
I can't be too proud to accept.
While we can.
Zhao Fengsheng.
I've been gone for a few days,
and you've taken over my casino?
Should I praise you,
or should I beat you up?
I, Zhao, am not very capable,
but I've earned Second Master's trust.
If you're unhappy about it,
go complain to your father.
Do you know who you're talking to?
Just a dog,
daring to block its master?
Young Master Tang.
In this world, you have to follow the rules.
If we're talking about dogs and masters,
it's not your place to say so.
Second Master said
casino matters are reported directly to him.
So there's no need for you to intervene.
You're lecturing me about rules?
Fine.
Then, as the General Manager of the Tang Group,
I'd like to see
what skills you have to hold my casino.
What do you mean?
Play a game with me.
If you win,
the casino is yours to manage for now.
If you lose,
pack your things and get out immediately.
Hold on, hold on.
Stop.
Young Master Tang is setting up a game.
Move aside, move aside.
Get back, get back.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Young Master.
I'm just here to run the casino and make money.
Using gambling skills to beat you
isn't necessary.
How about I call Second Master
and ask him what he thinks?
Why go that far?
Since you don't dare gamble with me,
then kneel right here.
Kowtow to me twice.
Call me "Master" a couple of times.
Call him Master.
Call him Master! Call him Master!
Shengzi already said he won't play.
Why are you pestering him?
If Young Master Tang's itching to gamble,
I'll play with you.
Miss Er Ni.
I didn't expect to see you here.
Zhao Fengsheng, you really are a coward.
For something like this,
you need a woman to stand up for you?
If you want to gamble, then gamble.
Too much talk makes you sound like a girl.
Trust me.
Someone like Young Master Tang,
who doesn't even dare sit at a woman's table,
has only this much skill.
And he has the nerve to call others cowards?
Interesting.
Compared to Qian Tianyu,
you suit my taste better.
A woman's card table or a woman's bed,
there's none I, Tang Huiyao, wouldn't dare get on.
Minimum bet is five thousand.
No maximum limit.
Dare to play?
Let's play then.
Deal the cards.
Twenty thousand.
Twenty thousand right off the bat?
Miss Er Ni is playing big.
None of your business.
Are you calling or not? Speak up.
Trying to bluff me from the start?
It's just twenty thousand.
I'll call.
Please show your cards.
Ace high.
Pair of Kings.
Young Master Tang.
Yours are so small,
and you dare show them off?
It's just one hand.
Continue.
Twenty thousand.
There are people watching the stairwell.
Tang Hongtu's office
won't be easy to get into.
Sorry.
Straight.
Beats yours.
The lady's luck is really good.
It's time for the shift change.
Young Master Tang.
You've lost so much already.
Where's your home-field advantage?
Deal.
Three of a Kind, Kings.
Lady Luck is smiling on me too.
It seems Miss Er Ni has a good hand.
Maybe I'm bluffing you again.
If I could die under Miss Er Ni's skirt,
I'd gladly be bluffed by you.
Disgusting.
All in.
Unless you have three Aces,
my hand is unbeatable.
It can't be that coincidental, right?
I see Young Master Tang is running low on chips.
Let this lady play one last hand with you.
I'm all in too.
How much is that?
Young Master Tang doesn't have enough chips, does he?
Yeah.
Such a big bet.
For the first time, I feel really poor.
No chips, no game.
Then I'll just take it all...
It's not over yet.
Don't be in such a hurry.
Don't forget whose turf this is.
Bring more chips.
Brother Tang really has the resources.
Yeah.
Young Master Tang is so eager to give me money.
My hand isn't small either.
And,
I have a feeling it's bigger than yours.
Then this lady will let you lose knowing why.
Three of a Kind, Kings
Three Kings!
She's going to win, right?
What a huge hand!
Young Master Tang is sure to lose this time.
Yeah.
Unless she has three Aces.
Exactly, exactly.
Sorry.
Three Aces.
Really?!
Miss Er Ni.
This is too outrageous.
You lose.
How can one hand possibly have
both three Kings and three Aces?
You're cheating, damn it!
Er Ni.
Don't make baseless accusations.
To accuse someone of cheating, you need proof.
Tell me, who's cheating?
Then why did you change the dealer just now?
This is the Tang Casino.
We change dealers on schedule.
Ask anyone here if that's not the case.
That's right.
Yeah! What, you can't accept it?
Little girl.
At the gambling table, you win some, you lose some.
You can't expect to win all the time.
So it's a setup, huh?
I'm done playing.
Er Ni.
Accusing my Tang Casino of cheating,
tarnishing our reputation like this...
We can't just let this slide.
What do you want?
Sit down.
Have a few drinks with me.
After a drink, we'll be friends.
I, Tang Huiyao, naturally won't give a friend a hard time.